Virginia Gildersleeve International Fund Records, 1969-2012
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. COMMITTEES
  - PART I.
    - Finance and investment, 1971-76 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Fundraising, 1969-76 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Internal auditing, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Nominating, 1971-72 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Strategic planning, 1986-88 (Box 12, Folder 13a)
    - Project grants
      - Project proposals, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 13b)
      - Correspondence, agendas, minutes, and reports
        - 1970-73 (Box 12, Folder 14-17)
        - Travel grants, 1970-71 (Box 12, Folder 18)
        - 1974-83 (Box 13, Folder 1-13)
        - 1984-92, undated (Box 14, Folder 1-9)
        - VGIFUW Request for grant for workshops on project management, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
        - Rejected proposals, 1984, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - International Federation of University Women
        - 17th Triennial Conference, 1970-71 (Box 15, Folder 1)
        - 56th Council, Philadelphia, USA, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 1a)
        - Pacific Regional Meeting, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 2)
        - General correspondence and memoranda, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 3)
        - 18th Triennial Conference, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
        - General correspondence and reports, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
        - IFUW grant applications, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 6)
        - Pre-Conference workshop, 1975-76 (Box 15, Folder 7)
        - 19th Triennial Conference, 1976-77 (Box 15, Folder 8)
        - General correspondence and reports, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 9)
        - 20th Triennial Conference, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
        - General correspondence and memoranda, 1978-86 (Box 15, Folder 11-14)
        - Archival project, 1985-88 (Box 15, Folder 15-16)
        - 22nd Triennial Conference: Workshop on Projects, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 17)
        - Relief Fund for Educational Purposes, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 18)
        - IFUW: Africa: Zimbabwe, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 19)
        - 23rd Triennial Conference
          - Workshop on Projects, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
          - Reports on funded IFUW projects, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
          - Luncheon, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 6)
          - Report on 23rd Conference, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
        - 24th Triennial Conference: Organizational Development Workshop, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
        - Africa
          - Advocates for African Food Security, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 1)
          - Botswana, 1974-75 (Box 17, Folder 2)
          - Egypt, 1978-79 (Box 17, Folder 3)
          - Ghana
            - Abakrampa Circuit Women's Assembly, 1990-91 (Box 17, Folder 4)
            - Bala Landlords' Association, 1990-91 (Box 17, Folder 5)
            - Federation of Ghana Business and Professional Women, 1986-87 (Box 17, Folder 6)
            - Women Palm-oil Producers Society, 1990-91 (Box 17, Folder 7)
          - Ivory Coast: Institute of Cultural Affairs, 1985-86 (Box 17, Folder 8)
          - Kenya
            - All Africa Conference of Churches, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 9)
            - National Council of Women of Kenya, 1985-86 (Box 17, Folder 10)
            - Ruhoti, Women's Group, 1985-88 (Box 17, Folder 11)
            - St. Frances Emergency Relief Fund
              - 1976-80, n.d (Box 17, Folder 12-13)
            - Other, 1977-87 (Box 17, Folder 14)
          - Lesotho, 1982-83 (Box 17, Folder 15)
          - Liberia, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 16)
          - Malawi, 1990-92 (Box 17, Folder 17)
          - Nigeria
            - Country Women Association of Nigeria, 1989-90 (Box 17, Folder 18)
            - Edom Women's Development Group, 1992-93 (Box 17, Folder 19)
            - Nigerian Association of University Women, 1990-91 (Box 17, Folder 20)
            - Other, 1982-92 (Box 17, Folder 21)
          - Senegal: AFFDU (French Association of University Women), Matam Valley, Women Association of Nabadji, 1989-93 (French language) (Box 17, Folder 22-24)
          - Sierra Leone, 1978-85 (Box 18, Folder 1-1a)
            [see also: Oversize materials]
          - Tanzania, 1975-86 (Box 18, Folder 2)
          - Uganda, 1976, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 3)
          - Zaire, 1986-87 (Box 18, Folder 4)
          - Zambia, 1974-76 (Box 18, Folder 5)
          - Zimbabwe
            - Mapondera, Esinet, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 6)
            - South African-Rhodesian Federation, 1975-76 (Box 18, Folder 7)
            - Zimbabwe Association of University Women, 1981-91 (Box 18, Folder 8)
            - Zimbabwe Women Finance Trust, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Asia
        - American Samoa, 1987-88 (Box 19, Folder 1)
        - Bangladesh, 1990-91 (Box 19, Folder 1b)
        - India
          - Association of Bhorden and Community Development, 1991-92 (Box 19, Folder 2)
          - Centre for Rural Development, 1990-91 (Box 19, Folder 3)
          - Holy Family Convent, 1989-93 (Box 19, Folder 4)
          - Indian Federation of University Women, 1974-86 (Box 19, Folder 5)
          - Literacy Manual for Field Workers, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
          - Little Flower Convent, 1991-93 (Box 19, Folder 7)
          - Project Calcutta 5-0, 1982-89 (Box 19, Folder 8)
            [see also: box 43, folder 7 and Audio visual materials]
          - Rosary Convent, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 9)
          - Winbread, 1988-91 (Box 19, Folder 10)
          - Other, 1979-92 (Box 19, Folder 11)
        - Indonesia, 1974, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 12)
        - Kiribati, 1989-90 (Box 19, Folder 13)
        - Korea
          - Korean Association of University Women, 1988-89 (Box 19, Folder 14)
          - Social Welfare Association of Cheji, 1989-90 (Box 19, Folder 15)
        - Pakistan
          - Institute of Educational and Vocational Guidance Figures, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 16)
          - Institute of Educational and Vocational Guidance for Girls, 1975-76, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 17)
          - Pakistan Federation of University Women, 1975-87 (Box 19, Folder 18-20)
        - Philippines
          - Metro-Manilla Council of Women, 1985-86 (Box 20, Folder 1)
          - Philippine Normal College, 1986-88 (Box 20, Folder 2-3)
          - Philippine Association of University Women, 1992-93 (Box 20, Folder 4)
          - Other, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 5)
        - Sri Lanka
          - Abeywickrama, Dorothy, 1974-82 (Box 20, Folder 6)
          - Alles, Jessica, 1989-90 (Box 20, Folder 7)
          - Sri Lankan Federation of University Women, 1974-79 (Box 20, Folder 8a-b)
        - Thailand, 1989-90 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Australia and New Zealand
        - Australian Federation of University Women, 1979-84 (Box 20, Folder 10)
        - Australian Federation of University Women, 1990-91 (Box 20, Folder 11)
        - New Zealand, 1971-86 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Canada
        - MATCH, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 13)
        - Canadian Federation of University Women, Africa/Canada Project, 1987-89 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Caribbean, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Central America
        - Costa Rica
          - Escuela, Ciencias Biologicas, 1992-94 (Box 21, Folder 1)
          - Fundacion Una, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 2)
        - El Salvador
          - Association of University Women of El Salvador Seminar, 1974-76 (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
          - Association of University Women of El Salvador Dental Project, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Europe
        - Belgium, Holland and Italy, 1974, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 6)
        - Denmark, 1974-86 (Box 21, Folder 7)
        - France, 1986-88 (Box 21, Folder 8)
        - Ireland, 1976-77 (Box 21, Folder 9)
        - United Kingdom
          - Associated Country Women of the World, 1978-82 (Box 21, Folder 10)
          - British Federation of University Women, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 11)
          - International Alliance of Women, 1976-86 (Box 21, Folder 12-14)
          - International Roster of Women Scholars and Professionals, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 15)
          - Lucy Cavendish College, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 1)
          - Theodora Bosanquet Bursary, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 2)
          - World Association of Girl Guides and Girl Scouts, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 3)
          - Other, 1976-84 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Middle East: Iran, 1969-70 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - South America
        - Argentina
          - Fondacion Para Estudio e Investigacion de la Mujer, 1991-92 (Box 22, Folder 6)
          - Other, 1976-87 (Box 22, Folder 7)
        - Brazil, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 8)
        - Colombia, 1986-88 (Box 22, Folder 9)
        - Guatemala, 1990-91 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - United States
        - American Association of University Women, 1971-78
          - Communication Between Cultures, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 11a)
          - One World: The Rich and the Poor, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 11b)
          - Pacific Basin Conference, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 12-13)
          - Archives Project, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 14)
        - Asian Women's Institute, 1975-86 (Box 23, Folder 1-6)
        - League of Women Voters, Overseas Education Fund, East Malaysia: Kuching Seminar, 1975-78 (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
        - Other projects, 1970-85 (Box 23, Folder 9-11)
  - PART II.
    - College Outreach ("Connections"): emails, 2001-02, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Constitution and by-laws
      - General correspondence and memoranda, 1984-99, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Committee working rules: correspondence and memoranda, 1986-2001 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Development Committee
        - General correspondence, memoranda, reports and brochures, 1996-99 (Box 36, Folder 4)
        - Special Committee on Corporate and Major Donors: minutes and reports, 1994-96 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Finance and Investment: agenda and chart, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Global Network
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1993-2000 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Directories and reports, 1991-99 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - House: correspondence, memoranda, and reports, 2001-02 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Membership Development
      - Correspondence, 1993-94, 1996-2002 (Box 36, Folder 10-11)
      - Agendas, minutes, reports, and brochures, 1990-2001 (Box 36, Folder 12-14)
    - Nominating: reports, 1996-99 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Special Events: email and report, 1998-99 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Strategic Planning: emails and reports, 1987-2001 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Project Grants
      - Grant application information, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Reports and related correspondence, 1993-99 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Grant application summaries, 1989-94, 1996-2000 (Box 37, Folder 6-14)
      - Grants chronologies, 1970-2001 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - American Association of University Women conferences and conventions: emails and memoranda, 1984-2001 (Box 37, Folder 16-19)
      - International Federation of University Women
        - Conferences
          - Graz, Switzerland (Base Camp I): correspondence, memoranda, and reports, 1995-99 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
          - Helsinki, Finland: correspondence and report, 1987-89 (Box 38, Folder 3)
          - Ottawa, Canada (Base Camp II): memoranda and photographs, 1999, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 4)
          - Yokohama, Japan: correspondence, memoranda, and reports, 1992-95 (Box 38, Folder 5-6)
      - NGO Forum on Women, Beijing, China
        - Correspondence and memoranda, 1995-96 (Box 38, Folder 7)
        - Look at the World Through Women's Eyes: Plenary Speeches from the NGO Forum on Women, Beijing '95 (Box 38, Folder 8)
        - Forum '95: The Independent Daily of the NGO Forum on Women, compilation of nine issues published each day throughout the Forum (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - Look at the World Through Women's Eyes: NGO Forum on Women, Beijing '95: Final Report (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Africa
        - African Action on AIDS, 1991-97 (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - Education in Africa: articles, 2000-01 (Box 39, Folder 4)
        - Cameroon
          - Alamatsom Community School, 1996-98 (Box 39, Folder 5)
          - Alamatsom School: photographs. 1997-98 (Box 40, Folder 1)
          - Cameroon University of Women, 1998-99 (Box 40, Folder 2)
          - Ntarbang Womens' Group, 2000-01 (Box 40, Folder 3)
        - Ghana
          - Abakrampa Women's Assembly, 1989-92 (Box 40, Folder 4)
          - Akpafu Mempeasem Farmers' Group, 1991-96 (Box 40, Folder 5)
          - Diagnostic Womens' Movement, 1997-2001 (Box 40, Folder 6)
          - Fetish Slave Liberation Movement: reports and photographs, 1994-97 (Box 40, Folder 7)
          - Fetish Slave Liberation Movement, 1999-2000, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
          - Ghanaian Association of University Women, 1995-98 (Box 40, Folder 9)
          - Lotus Children's Centre, 1999-2001 (Box 40, Folder 10)
          - Traditional Birth Attendants Women's Association, 1997-2001 (Box 40, Folder 11)
          - Women Are the Key Female Human Rights. 1996-2001 (Box 40, Folder 12)
        - Kenya
          - Kasaya Senior Women's Group, 1998-2000 (Box 41, Folder 1)
          - St. Jude Jumuiya Self Help Group, 1999-2001 (Box 41, Folder 2)
        - Nigeria
          - Farmers' Multi-purpose Cooperative Society, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 3)
          - Nigeria Association of University Women, 1990-91 (Box 41, Folder 4)
          - Nwanoka Okechukwu, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 5)
          - Edom Women Development Group, 1990-93 (Box 41, Folder 6)
          - UGO Women Development Group, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 7)
        - Senegal, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 8)
        - Sierra Leone (Box 41)
          - Kantia Agricultural Project, 1993-94 (Box 41, Folder 9)
          - Lembema Community Development Association, 1994-95 (Box 41, Folder 10)
          - Mataska Descendants Farming Project, 1992-95 (Box 41, Folder 11)
          - Makerere University Department of Women's Studies, 1996-99 (Box 41, Folder 12)
          - Network Movement for Justice and Development, 1998-2000 (Box 41, Folder 13)
          - Women Development Training Centre, 1992-95 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Uganda
        - Action for Development, 2000-01 (Box 41, Folder 15)
        - Keep Girls in School, 2000-02 (Box 41, Folder 16)
        - Zimbabwe, 1978-89 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Asia
        - Bangladesh
          - Organization for Mothers and Infants, 1997-2001 (Box 42, Folder 1a)
          - Shishu Niloy, 1989-92 (Box 42, Folder 1b)
          - Welfare Efforts, 1991-93 (Box 42, Folder 1c)
          - Women Development Unit 1992 (Box 42, Folder 1d)
        - Bhutan, circa 1990-2001 (Box 42, Folder 1e)
        - Fiji
          - Fiji Association of Women Graduates, 1998-99 (Box 42, Folder 2)
          - Girmit Council of Women, 1998-2000 (Box 42, Folder 3)
        - India
          - Projects review report, circa 1995 (Box 42, Folder 4)
          - A1 Poor Fund Foundation of India, 1998-99 (Box 42, Folder 5)
          - Association of Bhoodan and Community Development, 1987-91 (Box 42, Folder 6)
          - Calcutta 5-0, 1994-96 (Box 42, Folder 7)
            [see also: box 19, folder 8 and Audiovisual materials]
          - Centre for Human Resource Development, 1990-93 (Box 42, Folder 8)
          - Centre for Rural Development, 1989-91 (Box 42, Folder 9)
          - Congregation of Immaculate Conception, 1994-96 (Box 42, Folder 10)
          - Deepa Oil Convent, 1995-96 (Box 42, Folder 11)
          - Development Association for Women Needs, 1997-99 (Box 42, Folder 12)
          - Goa Association for Education and Development, 1993-95 (Box 42, Folder 13)
          - Holy Family Convent, 1989-94 (Box 42, Folder 14)
          - Indian Federation of University Women, 1993-98 (Box 42, Folder 15-16)
          - Indian Women Scientists Association, 1995-96 (Box 43, Folder 1)
          - Indian Social Service Institute, 1993-95 (Box 43, Folder 2)
          - Little Flower Convent, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 3)
          - Manchi Samariya Mahila Mandali, 1996-97 (Box 43, Folder 4)
          - Puthucuruchy Mahila Samajam, 1994-95 (Box 43, Folder 5)
          - Rehabilitation Centre for the Handicapped, 1996-97 (Box 43, Folder 6)
          - Society for Women and Downtrodden Development, 1992-98 (Box 43, Folder 7)
          - Vivek Chetana, 1991-95 (Box 43, Folder 8)
          - Win Bread, 1995-97 (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - Korea, 1988-96 (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - Nepal
          - Asmita Women's Publication House, 1997-2000 (Box 43, Folder 11)
          - Nepal Association of University Women, 1995-98 (Box 43, Folder 12)
        - Philippines
          - Arugaan Development Society, 1991-94 (Box 43, Folder 13)
          - Mary and Martha Ministries, 1995-96 (Box 43, Folder 14)
          - Metro Manila Council of Women, 1986-87 (Box 43, Folder 15)
          - Philippines Association of University Women
            - 1991-93 (Box 43, Folder 16)
            - 1992 (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
          - Science and Technology Advisory Council, 1993-98 (Box 44, Folder 3)
          - Zonta Club of Iloilo City, 1998-99 (Box 44, Folder 4)
        - Solomon Islands
          - Niu Women's Association, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 5)
          - Wahere Women's Association, 1993-94 (Box 44, Folder 6)
        - Sri Lanka, 1988-91 (Box 44, Folder 7)
        - Tamil, 1994-95 (Box 44, Folder 8)
        - Thailand
          - Hill Tribes Resources and Development Center, 1995-98 (Box 44, Folder 9)
          - Tippan Navawongs Survey Project, 1988-89 (Box 44, Folder 10)
        - Vietnam, 1997-98 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - Western Samoa, 1995-96 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Australia, 1994-95 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Canada, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Caribbean: Jamaica, 1994-95 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Central America
        - Costa Rica, 1991-94 (Box 45, Folder 4)
        - El Salvador, 1995-97 (Box 45, Folder 5)
        - Guatemala, 1990-91 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Europe (Eastern and Western)
        - Albanian Women Federation, 1998-99 (Box 45, Folder 7-8)
        - Croatia, 1998-2000 (Box 45, Folder 9)
        - England, 1992-94 (Box 45, Folder 10)
        - France, 1993-96 (Box 45, Folder 11)
        - Hungary, 1996-98 (Box 45, Folder 12)
        - Lithuania, 1996-98 (Box 45, Folder 13)
        - Turkey, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - South America
        - Argentina
          - Argentina Federation of University Women, 1995-98 (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
          - FAAP, 1989-95 (Box 46, Folder 3)
          - FEIM, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 4)
        - Colombia, 1985-88 (Box 46, Folder 5)
        - Ecuador
          - Ariday International Foundation, 1996-97 (Box 46, Folder 6-7)
          - Women's Foundation, 1997-99 (Box 46, Folder 8)
          - Women's Foundation: reports, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous VGIF documents, 1999, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - PART III.
    - Governance/Bylaws, 1995-2012 (Box 56, Folder 1-10)
    - Events
      - Photographs, 2000-03 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Photographs: meetings (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - 30th Anniversary Conference at Barnard, 1999-2001 (Box 56, Folder 13-17)
      - 40th Anniversary Committee, 2010 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - 40th Anniversary trip to India, 2010 (Box 57, Folder 1-3)
    - Fund Raising Committee, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Reports, 1987-88 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Membership, grants track record 1983-88 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Public Relations Committee, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - College Internship Program, 2002-04 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Marketing Committee, 2004-07 (Box 57, Folder 9-11)
    - The Conservation Company Group marketing study, Apr 2011 (Box 57, Folder 12-13)
    - Committee on Committees, 2007 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Crisis Management Manual, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Task Force on Organizational Structure, 2007 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Palmer Endowment and House Committee, 2000-03 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Nominating Committee
      - 2002 (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - 2011-12 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Membership Committee
      - General, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 20)
      - Directory, 1998-2007 (Box 57, Folder 21-25)
      - Notes, 2006-11 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Special Social Position: dinner and theater arrangements, Apr 2005-Apr 2012 (Box 58, Folder 2-3)
    - Website, 2001-02 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Project grants
      - Lithuania: unidentified photograph, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Grants process description, Oct 2009 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Reports to Board, 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Status reports, Apr 1979-89 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Grants history and yearly list of grants, 1999-2004 (Box 58, Folder 9-20)
      - Grants list, Apr 2005-08 (Box 59, Folder 1-8)
      - On-Site Visit Committee 2002-10 (Box 59, Folder 9-23)
      - Note to archive, 2013 (Box 59, Folder 24)
      - Pilot projects and special solicitations
        - Tibet: Chungba Primary School, 2004-05 (Box 59, Folder 25-27)
          [see also: Audiovisual materials]
        - #2207 Bangladesh: Pally Badhue Kallan Sangstha (PBKA), 2004-08 (Box 59, Folder 28-31)
        - #2546 Croatia: Croatian Association of University Women (CAUW), 2005-06 (Box 59, Folder 32-34)
        - #2389 Ghana: Glory Women Fellowship, 2005-06 (Box 59)
          - 1 of 3 (Box 59, Folder 35)
          - 2-3 of 3 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
        - #2783 Sierra Leone: Agency for Rural Advancement (AFRA), 2006-08 (Box 60, Folder 3-4)
        - #2920 India: Narkeldanga Rehnuma-e-Niswaan, 2007 (Box 60, Folder 5-6)
        - Firelight Foundation, 2007-08 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - 1993-1998
        - #380 Philippines: Science and Technology Advisory Council (STIR), 1993 (Box 61, Folder 1)
        - #667 Sierra Leone: Rogballan Women's Development Organization (RWEDO), 1996 (Box 61, Folder 2)
        - #669 India: Mahila Sankshem Sangh (MASS), 1996 (Box 61, Folder 3)
        - #722 Ghana: Liati Datem Cooperative, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 4)
        - #729 Uganda: Makere University Department of Women's Studies, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 5)
        - #861 Ghana: Diagnostic Women's Movement for Science Development (DWMSD), 1998 (Box 61, Folder 6)
        - #936 Bangladesh: Kallyan Prochesta, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 7)
        - #943 India: Development Association for Women Needs (DAWN) Pickle-Making Project, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 8)
        - #950 Ghana: Women are the Key - Female Genital Mutilation (FGM), 1998 (Box 61, Folder 9)
        - #994 India: Society for Integrated Tribal Development, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - 1999
        - #1025 Ecuador: Fundacion de la Mujer (Box 61, Folder 11)
        - #1028 India: Indian Federation of University Women's Associations (Box 61, Folder 12)
        - #1062 Ghana: Traditional Birth Attendants Women's Association (Box 61, Folder 13)
        - #1148 Nepal: Asmita Women's Publication House (Box 61, Folder 14)
        - #1150 Guinea: Network Movement for Justice and Development (Box 61, Folder 15)
        - #1196 Fiji: Girmit Council of Women (Box 61, Folder 16)
        - #1290 Uganda Association of University Women (Box 61, Folder 17)
        - #1292 Albanian Women Federation (Box 61, Folder 18)
        - #1301 Estonian Association of University Women (Box 61, Folder 19)
        - #1303 Croatian Association of University Women (Box 61, Folder 20)
        - #1304 Bangladesh: Organization for Mothers and Infants (Box 61, Folder 21)
        - #1305 Fiji: Association of Women Graduates (Box 61, Folder 22)
        - #1309 South Africa: Association of Women Graduates (Box 61, Folder 23-26)
        - #1316 Philippines: Zonta Club of Iloilo City (Box 61, Folder 27)
        - #1317 Cameroon: Association of University Women (Box 61, Folder 28)
        - #1320 Ghana: Kujo Isegury Association (Box 61, Folder 29)
      - 2000
        - #1335 Nigeria: Ugo Women Development Group (Box 61, Folder 30)
        - #1346 Nepal: Bhutan Women and Children Organization (Box 61, Folder 31)
        - #1350 Kenya: St. Jude Jumuiya Self-Help Group (Box 61, Folder 32-33)